izarc.org 2019-03-24

# IZArc | Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site. 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Our privacy policy is in plain English and will only take a few moments to read and understand. 

**Site Tracking**  
We have a simple web statistics program running that tracks how many times each page is visited. When you visit a page, information is logged that contains your domain name (aol.com, for example), date, time, and pages visited. There is no personally identifiable information. The information we collect is: - Used to improve the content on our site. - Never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are a method of tracking information you enter on a web site using a file on your computer. We do use a cookie to log whether you've visited the site before. No personal information is written to the cookie at all. Our site doesn't use cookies. However, some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
